A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Speeches, Series 15 FA383
Rockefeller Archive Center
- March 25, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 435)
  Washington, DC; Alfred Sloan Fellows Meeting; commerce and industry, management of industry.
- April 3, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 436)
  Washington, DC; Outstanding Handicapped Federal Employees Awards; health, employment.
- NOT USED (Box 11, Folder 437)
- April 7, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 438)
  Washington, DC; Swearing-In Ceremony, Henry P. Smith III; miscellaneous.
- April 8, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 439)
  Washington, DC; Young American Awards Presentation, outstanding youth presented by Boy Scouts; youth.
- April 9, 1975 (canceled) (Box 11, Folder 440)
  Washington, DC; United States Government Savings Bonds Kick-Off Meeting.
- April 9, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 441)
  Washington, DC; American Newspaper Publisher's Association; federal spending, energy, environment.
- April 10, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 442)
  Washington, DC; President's Commission on Personnel Interchange; economy, free enterprise.
- April 10, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 443)
  Washington, DC; Meeting with White House Fellows; Vice President's responsibilities.
- April 11, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 444)
  Washington, DC; National Association of Manufacturers; productivity.
- April 13, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 445)
  Chiang-Kai-Shek Funeral Statement.
- April 15, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 446)
  Washington, DC; Reception, Senate-House Dinner; introduction of Ford and his policies.
- April 15, 1975 (canceled) (Box 11, Folder 447)
  Washington, DC; National Commission on International Women's Year.
- April 15, 1975 (canceled) (Box 11, Folder 448)
  Washington, DC; Republican Senate/House Dinner.
- April 18, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 449)
  Boca Raton, FL; The Young President's Organization; productivity, economy, free enterprise.
- April 23, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 450)
  Washington, DC; The Advertizing Council, Inc.; free enterprise.
- April 23, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 451)
  Washington, DC; Presentation of Shakespeare Books.
- April 23, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 452)
  Washington, DC; Reception and Banquet, National Academy of Engineering, Presentation of first Marconi International Fellowship; science and technology.
- April 24, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 453)
  Washington, DC; American Revolution Bicentennial Exhibit; 175th Anniversary for the Library of Congress.
- April 24, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 454)
  Washington, DC; National Volunteer Awards; government.
- April 24, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 455)
  New York; New York Senate Campaign Committee Fund-Raiser; Republican Party.
- April 29, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 456)
  Washington, DC; Garden Clubs of America; environment.
- April 29, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 457)
  Washington, DC; International Session of the United States Chamber of Commerce; government, regulation.
- April 30, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 458)
  Washington, DC; King Hussein Dinner; toast.
- May 1, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 459)
  Washington, DC; National Urban Coalition Steering Committee; Domestic Council, revenue sharing.
- May 6, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 460)
  Washington, DC; Institutional Investors Institute; free enterprise.
- May 6, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 461)
  Washington, DC; Capitol Hill Club Reception Honoring Vice President; Ford.
- May 7, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 462)
  Washington, DC; Toast to Australian Prime Minister; toasts.
- May 7, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 463)
  Washington, DC; Archives of American Art; art.
- May 9, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 464)
  Hot Springs, VA, The Homestead; Business Council; free enterprise, energy, economy.
- May 12, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 465)
  Washington, DC; Federal City Council Board of Trustees Luncheon; cities.
- May 13, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 466)
  New York, Museum of Modern Art; Reception; art.
- May 14, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 467)
  Washington, DC; Long Island Businessmen Meeting; productivity.
- May 15, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 468)
  Washington, DC; National Press Club, Bill Miller; testimonial.
- May 16, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 469)
  Washington, DC; Republican Heritage Groups; ethnics.
- May 17, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 470)
  Washington, DC; Dinner, Shah of Iran; toast.
- May 18, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 471)
  Pocantico Hills, NY; Dinner, Shah of Iran; toasts.
- May 19, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 472)
  National Conference on Capital Investment and Employment.
  General note
  (no speech in file)
- May 20, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 473)
  Washington, DC; Meeting, Congressional Black Caucus; African Americans.
- May 21, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 474)
  Washington, DC; Bull Elephant's Luncheon; government.
- May 21, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 475)
  Washington, DC; Recording for the Blind Awards; handicapped, health.
- May 21, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 476)
  Washington, DC; Galo Plaza Dinner; testimonial.
- May 28, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 477)
  Washington, DC; Swearing-In of Ambassador William Lane; miscellaneous.
- May 28, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 478)
  Washington, DC; Task Group Meeting; drugs.
- May 29, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 479)
  Washington, DC; White House Fellows Reunion; miscellaneous.
- May 30, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 480)
  Washington, DC; United States-Romanian Economic Council; foreign relations.
- June 4, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 481)
  Annapolis, MD; United States Naval Academy commencement Exercises; defense.
- June 4, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 482)
- June 4, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 483)
  Washington, DC; New York Stock Exchange.
- June 6, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 484)
  Washington, DC; Sigma Delta Chi, National Press Club; media.
- June 6, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 485)
  Washington, DC; Testimony before Senator Kennedy's Joint Science Committee; science.
- June 10, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 486)
  Washington, DC; Testimony before Congressman Teague's Science and Technology Committee; science.
- June 12, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 487)
  New York; New York State Republican Committee Luncheon.
- June 12, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 488)
  New York; New York State Republican Committee Dinner; Republican Party.
- June 23, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 489)
  Washington, DC; Work Productivity Meeting; productivity.
- June 24, 1975 (Empty folder) (Box 12, Folder 490)
  Washington, DC; National Productivity Conference; productivity.
- July 9, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 491)
  Atlanta, GA; Public Meeting, National Commission on Water Quality; environment.
- July 10, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 492)
  Washington, DC; Meeting of Mayors; revenue sharing.
- July 16, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 493)
  Washington, DC; Meeting with Science Youth Group; science.
- July 22, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 494)
  Cincinnati, OH; Midwest Governors' Conference; energy.
- August 5, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 495)
  Washington, DC; White House Summer Interns; miscellaneous, Vice President's duties.
- August 5, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 496)
  Washington, DC; Congress of the Deaf; health.
- August 6, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 497)
  Washington, DC; Health Care Productivity Center; productivity, health.
- August 6, 1975 (canceled) (Box 12, Folder 498)
  Washington, DC; Compensation Panel Hearings.
- August 22, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 499)
  Seal Harbor, ME; Maine Republican Reception; Republican Party.
- August 26, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 500)
  Mobile, AL; Lieutenant Governors Conference; Domestic Council forums.
- August 27, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 501)
  Columbia, SC; GOP Reception.
- August 27, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 502)
  Columbia, SC; Gov. Edwards' Luncheon; Republican Party re the South.
- September 5, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 503)
  Rochester, NY; Dedication of Family Medical Center at Highland Hospital; health.
- September 5, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 504)
  Greece, NY; Dedication of Park Ridge Hospital; health.
- September 5, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 505)
  Rochester, NY; United States Savings Bond Drive; savings bonds.
- September 5, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 506)
  Rochester, NY; Monroe County Chairman's Club Reception; Monroe County.
- September 10, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 507)
  Washington, DC; Capitol Hill Club Reception; Ford and his Administration.
- September 10, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 508)
  Washington, DC; Savings Bond Award Ceremony; savings bonds.
- September 11, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 509)
  Washington, DC; "Life Magazine" Bicentennial Issue; Bicentennial.
- September 12, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 510)
  Little Rock, AR; Arkansas events; Winthrop Rockefeller & Republican Party.
- September 12, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 511)
  Dallas, TX; National Federation of Republican Women Convention; women, government, Republican Party.
- September 13, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 512)
  Enid, OK; Airport Reception.
- September 13, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 513)
  Enid, OK; Republican Dinner; energy, domestic programs.
- September 13, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 514)
  Norman, OK; GOP Campaign Brunch; miscellaneous information about Oklahoma.
- September 15, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 515)
  London, England, British Museum; "The World of Franklin and Jefferson" Bicentennial Exhibit; bicentennial.
- September 17, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 516)
  Washington, DC, National Archives; Reading Is Fundamental Ceremony; bicentennial.
- September 18, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 517)
  Washington, DC, State Department; National Medal of Science Luncheon; science.
- September 18, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 518)
  Washington, DC; British Embassy Dinner in honor of Member of Parliament Margaret Thatcher; NAR Toast to Mrs. Thatcher.
- September 24, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 519)
  Washington, DC; Vice President's Office; Presentation of "Pulick Occurrences," (first newspaper); Bicentennial, journalism.
- September 26, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 520)
  Pocantico, NY; County Chairmen's Luncheon; Republican Party (New York state).
- September 29, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 521)
  Washington, DC, Madison Hotel; Federal City Council Meeting; government.
- October 2, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 522)
  Washington, DC, Madison Hotel; The National Energy Project Conference; energy.
- October 3, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 523)
  Portland, OR; Western States Republican Breakfast; miscellaneous.
- October 3, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 524)
  Portland, OR; Republican Reception; miscellaneous.
- October 3, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 525)
  Portland, OR; Western States Republican Conference; Republican Party.
- October 6, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 526)
  Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Energy Independence Authority Briefing; energy.
- October 7, 1975 (canceled) (Box 13, Folder 527)
  Washington, DC, Shoreham Hotel; "Change" Magazine Luncheon.
- October 7, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 528)
  Kings Mountain, NC; Kings Mountain Bicentennial Celebration; bicentennial.
- October 8, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 529)
  Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Roundtable on Privacy and Information; privacy.
- October 10, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 530)
  Washington, DC; Toast to King Olav; toast.
- October 11, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 531)
  Newport News, VA; Eisenhower Ship Launching; defense, navy.
- October 11, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 532)
  New York, Waldorf Astoria; Columbus Day Dinner; New York City.
- October 15, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 533)
  Columbus, OH; Republican Leadership Meeting; Republican Party.
- October 15, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 534)
  Columbus, OH; Republican State Committee Dinner; inflation, defense, government.
- October 16, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 535)
  Charleston, WV; Executive Club Luncheon; energy.
- October 16, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 536)
  Charleston, WV; West Virginia Reception; Ford and his policies.
- October 16, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 537)
  Roanoke, VA; GOP Fund-Raising Reception; Republican Party.
- October 21, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 538)
  Denver, CO; Public Forum on Domestic Policy; Domestic Council.
- October 22, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 539)
  Washington, DC; Republican Congressional Wives Luncheon; miscellaneous re Congressional wives.
- October 22, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 540)
  Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Congressman Brown Visit; talking points on energy.
- October 23, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 541)
  Indianapolis, IN; GOP Luncheon; economy.
- October 23, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 542)
  Indianapolis, IN; Indiana State Teachers Association; education.
- October 23, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 543)
  Indianapolis, IN; GOP Reception; miscellaneous.
- October 23, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 544)
  Decatur, IL; Macon County Republican Dinner; politics, domestic problems.
- October 24, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 545)
  Milwaukee, WI; Business-Labor Luncheon; government, domestic problems.
- October 24, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 546)
  Milwaukee, WI; Founders Club Reception; Republican Party.
- October 24, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 547)
  Milwaukee, WI; United Negro College Fund Dinner; African-Americans, education.
- October 29, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 548)
  Tampa, FL; Domestic Public Forum; Domestic Council.
- October 30, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 549)
  Pocantico, NY; Lunch with President Sadat; toast.
- October 30, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 550)
  New York; Hebrew Union College; religion.
- October 31, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 551)
  Houston, TX; Dinner for President Sadat; toast.
- November 5, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 552)
  Washington, DC, Capitol Hill; Foreign Relations Committee Luncheon for President Sadat; toast.
- November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 553)
  Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Presentation of Labor Department Design Manual; miscellaneous.
- November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 554)
  Austin, TX; Conference of Women in Public Life; women.
- November 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 555)
  Austin, TX; Public Forum on Domestic Policy; Domestic Council.
- November 14, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 556)
  Kansas City, MO; Future Farmers of America; agriculture.
- November 14, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 557)
  Lincolnshire, IL; McClory Testimonial Dinner.
- November 15, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 558)
  St. Cloud, MN; Minnesota Republican State Convention; Republican Party.
- November 15, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 559)
  St. Paul, MN; Elephant Club Reception; government, Republican Party.
- November 15, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 560)
  St. Cloud, MN; Metropolitan State College; energy.
- November 15, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 561)
  St. Paul, MN; GOP Fund Raiser Dinner; Republican Party.
- NOT USED (Box 14, Folder 562)
- November 18, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 563)
  Philadelphia, PA; Public Forum on Domestic Policy; Domestic Council.
- November 19, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 564)
  Washington, DC; Council of 100 Dinner; African Americans.
- November 21, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 565)
  Wichita, KS; Republican Governors Conference; energy.
- November 21, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 566)
  Wichita, KS; Breakfast with Governors; Vice Presidential withdrawal, miscellaneous.
- November 21, 1975 (canceled) (Box 14, Folder 567)
  Wichita, KS; Luncheon with Kansas GOP Leaders.
- November 25, 1975 (canceled) (Box 14, Folder 568)
  New York; United Jewish Appeal Dinner; Jews, Middle East.
- November 25, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 569)
  Indianapolis, IN; Public Forum on Domestic Policy; Domestic Council.
- December 2, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 570)
  New York; New York State GOP Reception; local government.
- December 3, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 571)
  New York; NAR testimony before Urban Development Corporation Hearings (Moreland Act Commission); Urban Development Corporation (UDC), housing, revenue financing.
- December 3, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 572)
- December 4, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 573)
  Pittsburg, PA; Republican National Committee, Private Reception; Republican Party.
- December 4, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 574)
  Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Presentation of Federal Women Awards; women.
- December 4, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 575)
  Pittsburgh, PA; Republican Awards Dinner, Tribute to Hugh Scott; testimonial.
- December 5, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 576)
  New York; National Association of Manufacturers; energy.
- December 9, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 577)
  Los Angeles, CA; Public Forum on Domestic Policy; Domestic Council.
- December 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 578)
  Washington, DC; Council on Environmental Quality Luncheon; environment.
- December 10, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 579)
  Washington, DC; Booster Club Reception, Army-Navy Club; Republican Party, need to support incumbent Republican candidates.
- December 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 580)
  Nashville, TN; Republican State Committee Fund-Raising Luncheon; energy.
- December 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 581)
  Nashville, TN; Reception for Tennessee Contributors, Home of Pat Wilson; Republican Party.
- December 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 582)
  Houston, TX; GOP Cocktail Reception; Republican Party.
- December 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 583)
  Houston, TX; State GOP Reception (Black GOP Leaders); Blacks and Republican Party.
- December 11, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 584)
  Houston, TX; Houston Business & Professional Men's Club Dinner; economy.
- December 12, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 585)
  Houston, TX; Republican National Committee Reception; Republican Party.
- December 12, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 586)
  Houston, TX; Southern Republican Conference; federalism.
- December 15, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 587)
  Washington, DC, Senate Recording Studio, Capitol Hill; Taping for Uniformed Firefighters Association Film; firefighting.
- December 15, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 588)
  White House; Press Briefing; Domestic Council findings.
- December 17, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 589)
  Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Presentation of Department of Labor, Occupational, Safety, and Health Awards; health.
- January 2, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 590)
  Washington, DC; "Credit Suisse" article; bicentennial, federalism, government.
- January 8, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 591)
  Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Swearing-In of Advisory Committee on trade Negotiations; world trade.
- January 14, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 592)
  Washington, DC, Vice President's Office; Meeting of the Advisory Groups of Science and Technology; science and technology.
- January 14, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 593)
  Washington, DC, Shoreham Hotel; National Council of Farmer Coops Luncheon; energy and agriculture.
- January 19, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 594)
  Washington, DC, Rayburn House Office Building; National Commission on Water Quality Hearing; environment.
- January 19, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 595)
  Washington, DC, Capitol Hill; Opening of the Second Session of the 94th Congress; bicentennial.
- January 21, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 596)
  Washington, DC, Capitol Hill Club; Energy Independence Authority Breakfast; energy.
- January 21, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 597)
  Washington, DC, White House; Introduction of President Ford at the Presidential Budget/State of the Union briefing; Ford.
- January 26, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 598)
  Washington, DC, Bolling Air Force Officers Club; Military Wives; national, defense, foreign affairs.
- January 26, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 599)
  Salem, WV; Salem College Convocation; economy, science and technology.
- January 29, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 600)
  Rye, NY; Westchester County Republican Committee Annual Dinner; Republican Party.
- January 30, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 601)
  Dearborn, MI; Drop-In Reception for President Ford Committee; Ford.
- January 30, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 602)
  Dearborn, MI; Midwest Republican Leadership Conference Reception; Republican Party, economy, energy, foreign affairs.
- January 30, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 603)
  Dearborn, MI; Midwest Republican Leadership Conference Dinner; Republican Party.
- February 4, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 604)
  Washington, DC, New Senate Office Building; Senate Operations Committee Hearings; future and the Commission on Critical Choices.
- February 4, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 605)
  Washington, DC, Dirksen Senate Office Building; United States Senate Youth Program; youth; government.
- February 6, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 606)
  Washington, DC, Columbia Plaza; National Council on the Arts; arts, government role in.
- February 6, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 607)
  Washington, DC, Twin Bridges Marriott Hotel; Introduction of President Ford at Northeast Republican Leadership Conference; Ford, Republican Party.
- February 10, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 608)
  Washington, DC, Shoreham Hotel; Atomic Energy Forum Luncheon; energy, Energy Independence Authority.
- February 11, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 609)
  Miami, FL; Meeting with labor leaders; energy, Energy Independence Authority.
- February 12, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 610)
  Paris, KY; GOP Fund Raising Luncheon; Republican Party.
- February 12, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 611)
  Louisville, KY; Republican National Committee Fund Raiser Reception; Republican Party.
- February 12, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 612)
  Louisville, KY; GOP Lincoln Day Dinner; Lincoln, political freedom, economic freedom.
- February 14, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 613)
  New York, Waldorf Astoria; New York County Republican Committee Lincoln Day Dinner; Lincoln, New York City, Ford, fiscal problems.
- February 19, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 614)
  Washington, DC; National Press Club; Press Club Speech; government, problems with.
- February 19, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 615)
  Washington, DC; British Embassy; Toast to United States Ambassador Anne Armstrong; toast.
- February 20, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 616)
  Lansing, MI; Governor's Council Reception; Republican Party.
- February 20, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 617)
  Lansing, MI; Michigan State Republican Committee Bicentennial Dinner; economic freedom and individual freedom.
- February 23, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 618)
  Boston, MA; American Association for the Advancement of Science; science and technology.
- February 24, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 619)
  Washington, DC; National Governors' Conference; federal spending, revenue sharing, government and local government.
- February 25, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 620)
  Philadelphia, PA; Bicentennial Bishops and Connectional Church Council Banquet; religion, African-Americans.
- March 9, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 621)
  New York, Waldorf Astoria; Religion in American Life, religion.
- March 10, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 622)
  Washington, DC, Department of Commerce; National Industrial Energy Council; Energy Independence Authority, energy.
- March 12, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 623)
  Albuquerque, NM; Chairman's Club Reception; Republican Party.
- March 12, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 624)
  Albuquerque, NM; Lincoln Day Dinner; politics.
- March 16, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 625)
  Chicago, IL; National American Wholesale Grocers Association; agriculture and prices as related to energy, regulation.
- March 16, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 626)
  Chicago, IL; President Ford Committee Reception; Republican Party.
- March 17, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 627)
  Chicago, IL; Executives Club; economic freedom, commerce & industry, comparing founding fathers with present, government regulation.
- March 18, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 628)
  Washington, DC; Toast to Prime Minister of Ireland; toast.
- March 18, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 629)
  Washington, DC, Capitol Hill; Address to Joint Economic Committee; economic freedom.
- March 20-21, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 630)
  Tunisia; Toast to President & Mrs. Bourguiba, Departure Statement; Tunisia toasts.
- March 21-23, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 631)
  France; Arrival Statement, Toasts, Meeting, United States Embassy Staff, Ambassador Rush Toast, Remarks, Lafayette Tomb, Remarks, Rochambeau Tomb, Toast to President Giscard, Bicentennial, Departure Statement; France, Bicentennial, toasts.
- March 22, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 632)
  Paris, France; Bicentennial Speech; Bicentennial.
- March 23-26, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 633)
  Iran; Arrival Statement, Toast to Shah of Iran, Toast to Governor-General of Isfahan, Departure Statement; Iran, toasts.
- March 26-28, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 634)
  Malaysia; Arrival Statement, Remarks, Embassy Staff, American Community, Toast, Kuala Lumpur visit, Departure Statement; Malaysia, toasts.
- March 28, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 635)
  Singapore; Remark, American Business Leaders Reception, Toast, State Dinner; Singapore, toasts.
- March 30 - April 1, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 636)
  Australia; Arrival Statement, Canberra, Remarks to Embassy Staff, Canberra, Toast to Governor-General, Toast to Prime Minister, Canberra Departure Statement, Toast to Governor of New South Wales, Arrival Statement Sydney; Australia, toasts, Bicentennial.
- March 30 - April 1, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 637)